Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIV: Red Hot + Rhapsody
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Admission pass, 1998; cuid7962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Invitation envelopes, [n.d.]; cuid7963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Invitation package, 1998; cuid7964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Invitation pamphlet, 1998; cuid7965 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: VIP thank-you card, 1998; cuid7966 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Postcards - Red Hot + Rhapsody, 1998; cuid7967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, 1998; cuid7968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Programme: Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody, a Benefit for AIDS Relief, c.a. 1998; cuid7969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Promotional sampler: Levi's Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody / The Gershwin Groove, 1998; cuid7970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Promotional sampler: Selections from Red Hot + Rhapsody, 1998; cuid7971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Promotional sampler: Selections from Red Hot + Rhapsody, 1998; cuid7972 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Promotional single: "Summertime," Morcheeba featuring Hubert Laws; China Records Ltd, 1998; cuid7973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Promotional single: "Summertime," Morcheeba featuring Hubert Laws; China Records Ltd, 1998; cuid7974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody; Antilles Records (Promotional), 1998; cuid7975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody; Antilles Records (Promotional), 1998; cuid7976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Table tents - Red Hot + Rhapsody, [n.d.]; cuid7977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsals - Natalie Merchant, Bobby Womack, The Roots, Ernest Ranglin, Sarah Cracknell, Michael Franti, Spearhead, cuid7978 (Box 39)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Details Magazine photoshoot - Smoke City, Duncan Sheik, Baaba Maal, Michael Franti, Ernest Ranglin, cuid7979 (Box 39)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Details photoshoot + performance - Duncan Sheik, The Roots, Ernest Ranglin, Michael Franti, Baaba Maal, cuid7980 (Box 39)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Davina rehearsal, outside photographs of Webster Hall - Sarah Cracknell, The Roots, cuid7981 (Box 40)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsal - Duncan Sheik + Mission 12 - Hubert Laws, cuid7982 (Box 40)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsals: Bobby [Womack] & Hubert [Laws] - The Roots, cuid7983 (Box 41)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Details press conference - Natalie Merchant, Davina, Duncan Sheik, Saint Etienne, Smoke City, Spearhead, others (unidentified), cuid7984 (Box 41)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsal + press conference - The Roots, Natalie Merchant, Morcheeba, Sarah Cracknell, Hubert Laws, Duncan Sheik, Michael Franti, Ernest Ranglin, cuid7985 (Box 41)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - By George and Ira; PolyGram Records, 1998; cuid7986 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody; Antilles Records, 1998; cuid7987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Series XV: Optic Nerve: David Wojnarowicz on CD-ROM
  Optic Nerve: David Wojnarowicz on CD-ROM was released by Red Hot Organization in 1999. Optic Nerve was produced by Red Hot Organization and Funny Garbage in conjunction with the New Museum of Contemporary Art's exhibit, Fever: The Art of David Wojnarowicz. The CD-ROM encompasses music, writing, film, painting and performance by Wojnarowicz.
  Optic Nerve was originally available from the New Museum bookstore in New York City. $4 per unit from the sale of each disc was donated to the Hetrick Martin Institute, which Wojnarowicz supported during his lifetime.
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "Postcards from America, X-Rays from Hell: the life and times of David Wojnarowicz", 1990-1991; cuid7988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Attinello, Paul Gregory, 2000; cuid7989 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Invoices, 2000; cuid7990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Optic Nerve, 1998-1999; cuid7991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Wojnarowicz, 1999; cuid7992 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Wojnarowicz, David // Marion S., 1991-1994; cuid7993 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - "Angel with a Gun," article on David Wojnarowicz by John Carlin, 1992; cuid7994 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Art in America article on Wojnarowicz, 1990; cuid7995 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Press clippings, 1999; cuid7996 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Press release for readings from "Close to the Knives", 1991; cuid7997 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Optic Nerve; Red Hot Organization, 1999; cuid7998 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Subseries E: Videos
    Conditions Governing Access
    Repository permission is required for access. Please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu.
    - David Wojnarowicz Postcards from America Dailies Transfer, 1991; cuid8691; Wojnarowicz, David (Box 237, Cassette cuid8691)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      3/4" Umatic, 30 min.
    - David Wojnarowicz Tape 1, Selections from CDrom, 1998; cuid8692 (Box 237, Cassette cuid8692)
      Housing Annotation: "David in water upstate; Little house - upstate; Fear of Disclosure; Stray Dogs; Where Evil Dwells; You Killed Me First; Untitled from No Alternative"
      Betcam SP, 60 min.
    - David Wojnarowicz Tape 2, Selections from CDrom, 1998-12; cuid8695 (Box 237, Cassette cuid8695)
      Housing Annotations: "News from TV/dialog @NEA w/david; Property of Funny Garbage"
      Betacam SP, 60 min.
    - David Wojnarowicz Tape 3, Selections from CDrom, 1998-12; cuid8696 (Box 237, Cassette cuid8696)
      Housing Annotations: "Itsofomo Selections; Property of Funny Garbage"
    - Where Evil Dwells, 2001; cuid8693; Wojnarowicz, David; Turner, Tommy, 1959- (Box 237, Cassette cuid8693)
      Betcam SP, 33 min.
- Series XVI: Red Hot + Indigo
  Red Hot + Indigo, a Duke Ellington tribute, was released by Red Hot Organization in 2000, after an agreement for the album to be released by a record company fell through.
  All About the Blues is a compilation produced for Liz Claiborne, featuring women artists singing the blues.
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "All About the Blues," a Red Hot compilation for Liz Claiborne of legendary ladies singing the blues, 2000; cuid7999 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Agreements, 1999; cuid8000 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - All About the Blues / Liz Claiborne, 2000; cuid8001 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid8002 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Budget (Restricted), 1999; cuid8003 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Budgets/Expenses - Studio recordings (Restricted), 1998 - 2000; cuid8004 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Cinram, 2001; cuid8005 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Clearances - Liz [Claiborne] Thanks, cuid8006 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - CMG Worldwide, 1998-2003; cuid8007 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Contacts, [n.d.]; cuid8008 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Ellington estate, 1999; cuid8009 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Expenses (Restricted), 1999-2000; cuid8010 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Famous Music, 1999; cuid8011 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Invoices: 1.800 Postcards, 2001; cuid8012 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Label and artist agreements, 1999-2000; cuid8013 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Les Nubians, 1999; cuid8014 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Licensed tracks, 1998-2000; cuid8015 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Lizwear / CD Book. Job / 6.29.00 ..., 2000; cuid8016 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      2 CD-Rs, 650 MB
    - Medeski Martin & Wood + guests, 1999; cuid8017 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - On Ellington, 1998, 2000; cuid8018 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Paid bills (Restricted), 1999; cuid8019 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Publishing, 1999; cuid8020 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Publishing waivers, 1999; cuid8021 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Recording costs (Restricted), 1999; cuid8022 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - RHO - All About the Blues / 9.12.00, 2000; cuid8023 (Box 16, Folder 54)
      CD-R: 650 MB
    - Seliger auction contacts, 1999; cuid8024 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Seliger auction winners, 2001; cuid8025 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Seliger auction winners, 2001; cuid8026 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Terry, Clark, 1999; cuid8027 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - To file (Restricted), 1999-2000; cuid8028 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Tortoise, 1999; cuid8029 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Track-by-track expenses (Restricted), 1999-2000; cuid8030 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - All About the Blues; Red Hot Organization, 2000; cuid8031 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - All About the Blues; Red Hot Organization, [n.d.]; cuid8032 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Postcards - Red Hot + Indigo, cuid8033 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, 2001; cuid8034 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Press release, 2001; cuid8035 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Indigo; Red Hot Organization, 2000; cuid8036 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Series XVII: Artists Against AIDS Worldwide - "What's Goin' On"
  What's Going On was released in 2001 by Sony in collaboration with Artists Against AIDS Worldwide (AAAW), featuring remakes of Marvin Gaye's "What's Going On." AAAW was founded by Leigh Blake, co-founder of Red Hot Organization. (Reference: Amazon.com)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - AAAW (Restricted), 2001-2002; cuid8037 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - AAAW 2, 2001-2002; cuid8038 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Benefit loan, 2001; cuid8039 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Execution releases, 2001; cuid8040 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Letter of intent, 2002; cuid8041 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Royalties, 2002; cuid8042 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Royalties + Expenses, 2001-2002; cuid8043 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Series XVIII: Red Hot + Riot
  Red Hot + Riot, a Fela Kuti tribute, was released by MCA Records in 2002. The album features Femi Kuti, Fela Kuti's son. A companion film, Red Hot + Riot: Encounters with AIDS in Africa, was released by Red Hot Organization. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "Gentleman" / Warner Bros. TV license, 2003-2004; cuid8044 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - 1.800 Postcards, 2002; cuid8045 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Agreements (Restricted), 2002-2003; cuid8046 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Artist agreements (Restricted), 2000-2003; cuid8047 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid8048 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Barclays / MCA Records, 2002-2003; cuid8049 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Colomentality, 2001; cuid8050 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Contact information, 2002; cuid8051 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Contacts, [n.d.]; cuid8052 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 2002; cuid8053 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Durban contact information, [n.d.]; cuid8054 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Durban expenses (Restricted), 2000; cuid8055 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Durban expenses, 2000; cuid8056 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - DVD, 2002; cuid8057 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - DVD / The New Museum of Contemporary Art, 2003; cuid8058 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Expenses - Red Hot + Durban, 2000; cuid8059 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Expenses - Red Hot + Lagos (Restricted), 2000; cuid8060 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Family Affair (Restricted), 2001; cuid8061 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Fefe Na Efe (Restricted), [n.d.]; cuid8062 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Gentleman (Restricted), 2001; cuid8063 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Invoices (Restricted), 2000 - 2002; cuid8064 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Invoices (Restricted), 2000 - 2001; cuid8065 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Invoices / Budget (Restricted), 2001-2002; cuid8066 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Lagos, 1999-2000; cuid8067 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Lagos contacts, [n.d.]; cuid8068 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Lagos expenses, 2000; cuid8069 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Lagos release forms, 2000; cuid8070 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Marketing, 2002-2003; cuid8071 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Me'Shell NdegéOcello session, 2001-2002; cuid8072 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Mortensen mess, 2000-2001; cuid8073 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - No Agreement!!, 2000-2002; cuid8074 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Paul [Heck]'s expenses, 2001; cuid8075 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Red Hot 1, [n.d.]; cuid8076 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Zip disk: MAC100, 100 MB.
    - Red Hot 2, [n.d.]; cuid8077 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Zip disk: PC100, 100 MB.
    - Red Hot Organization, [n.d.]; cuid8078 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Zip disk: 100 MB.
    - Sade "By Your Side", 2000-2002; cuid8079 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Shakara / Lady (Restricted), 2001; cuid8080 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Shuffering & Shmiling (Restricted), 2000-2001; cuid8081 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Signed (Restricted), 2002-2003; cuid8082 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Sorrow Tears + Blood (Restricted), 2000-2001; cuid8083 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Trouble Sleep; Yanga Wake Am (Restricted), 2000-2001; cuid8084 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Video releases (Restricted), 2000-2002; cuid8085 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Water No Get Enemy session / invoices (Restricted), 2000-2002; cuid8086 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Zombie, 2000-2002; cuid8087 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Ads - Red Hot + Riot, 2002; cuid8088 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Best Albums of 2002, cuid8089 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Online press, 2002; cuid8090 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Postcards - Red Hot + Riot, 2002; cuid8091 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings, 2002; cuid8092 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Press clippings, 2002 - 2003; cuid8093 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Press clippings compiled by Music Corporation of America, 2002; cuid8094 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Press in magazines, 2000 - 2002; cuid8095 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Press release, 2001; cuid8096 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Red Hot + Riot: Encounters with AIDS in Africa; Red Hot Organization, 2003; cuid8097 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      DVD
    - Reviews, 2002; cuid8098 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photographs, [n.d.]; cuid8099 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Riot; MCA Records, 2002; cuid8100 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
  - Subseries A: Administration Files, American Express folders contain account information. Same for Checks, Cheque books, Deposits, Monthly accounting statements, Padell Nadell etc, Martin Greene Ravden folders, Bank statement folders, Information Document Request folders
    amfAR stands for American Foundation for AIDS Research. (http://www.amfar.org)
    Financial files (receipts, bills, etc.) may have been processed on box level only.
    - "We're All In This Together", 1994; cuid8101 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 1994 payroll taxes (Restricted), 1994 - 1996; cuid8102 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Accounting, 1993 - 1994; cuid8103 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - ACT UP: Aids Coalition To Unleash Power, 1992; cuid8104 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Agreements, 1991; cuid8105 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Amazon.com auction, 2001; cuid8106 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - American Express, 1994 - 1995; cuid8107 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - American Express, 1996; cuid8108 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - American Express, 1997-1998; cuid8109 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - American Express, 2000; cuid8110 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - American Express: Correspondence and Quarterly Management Reports, 1996 - 1997; cuid8111 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Annual "closed books" reports and accounts, 1993-1995; cuid8112 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Arista Records, Inc., 1995-1997; cuid8113 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bank reconciliations - Checking, 1994; cuid8114 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Bank reconciliations - Multiple, 1996 - 2000; cuid8115 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bank reconciliations - Signature Bank, 2001; cuid8116 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Bank statements - Chemical Bank, 1994; cuid8117 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Bank statements - HSBC Bank, 2000; cuid8118 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bank statements - HSBC Bank, 2001; cuid8119 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Bank statements and checks - Republic National Bank, 1996; cuid8120 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Bank statements - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8121 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Bank statements - Republic National Bank, 2000; cuid8122 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Bank statements - Signature Bank, 2001-2002; cuid8123 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - BCL Entertainment Corp. (Merchandising), 1993-1995; cuid8124 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Bills (Restricted), 2001; cuid8125 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bills, paid: A--B, 1994; cuid8126 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bills, paid: C, 1994; cuid8127 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bills, paid: C, 1994; cuid8128 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Bills, paid: D--P, 1994; cuid8129 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Bills, paid: Q--Z, 1994; cuid8130 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): A--B, 1994; cuid8131 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): C, 1994; cuid8132 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): D--G, 1994; cuid8133 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): H--Z, 1994; cuid8134 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1996; cuid8135 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1996; cuid8136 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Bills, paid: C--D, 1996; cuid8137 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Bills, paid: E--F, 1996; cuid8138 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Bills, paid: G--N, 1996; cuid8139 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Bills, paid: P, 1996; cuid8140 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Bills, paid: Q--Z, 1996; cuid8141 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1999; cuid8142 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bills, paid: B--N, 1999; cuid8143 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Bills, paid: O--W, 1999; cuid8144 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Bills, paid: A--C (Restricted), 2000; cuid8145 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Bills, paid: D--U (Restricted), 2000; cuid8146 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Blank forms, "List of Business Expenses", [n.d.]; cuid8147 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - BMG donation, 1995; cuid8148 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 2000; cuid8149 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1996; cuid8150 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1997; cuid8151 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1998; cuid8152 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1999-2001; cuid8153 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports; check transaction reports, 1996-1997; cuid8154 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports; check transaction reports, 1999-2000; cuid8155 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Cellular One Savings Book, 1994; cuid8156 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Checks, 1994-1995; cuid8157 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Checks, 1997-1998; cuid8158 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Chemical Bank, 1996; cuid8159 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Cheque books, Barclays Bank, 1991-1992; cuid8160 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Chrysalis Records / amfAR loan repayment, 1991-1995; cuid8161 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Clark, Larry film treatment, 1993; cuid8162 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Restricted), 1996-1999; cuid8163 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (Restricted), 1996; cuid8164 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Davis Polk & Wardwell, 1995; cuid8165 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Dead Meat [Sue Coe], 1997; cuid8166 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Delaware corporation - Not-for-profit, 1994; cuid8167 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Deposit slips, 1994; cuid8168 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Deposit slips, 1996; cuid8169 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Deposit slips, 2000; cuid8170 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Deposit slips - HSBC Bank, 2001; cuid8171 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8172 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8173 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8174 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Deposit slips - Signature Bank, 2001-2002; cuid8175 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Detailed ledger by job, 1995-1996; cuid8176 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Dissolution of The Red Hot Organisation Limited (UK), 1995-1996; cuid8177 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - EasyPay tax reports (Restricted), 1999; cuid8178 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - ECD - paid bills, 1996; cuid8179 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Egan, Nick, 1991; cuid8180 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Exempt Organization Certifications, 1995-1997; cuid8181 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Expenses above and beyond, 1994-1995; cuid8182 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Expenses: Federal Express /Messengers, 1995; cuid8183 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Feinstein Management, 1996; cuid8184 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Finances, 1999; cuid8185 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Financial matters - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994; cuid8186 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Financial reports, 1995-1996; cuid8187 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Financial statement, 1996; cuid8188 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - First Institutional Securities, LLC, 1998-2001; cuid8189 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Fleet Bank - petty cash; statements, 1998-2000; cuid8190 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Form 990 - Grants, Allocations and Payments to Affiliates and Others, 2002; cuid8191 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - From Movieplay, [n.d.]; cuid8192 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      SyQuest 200 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge
    - Funding/collaboration requests from HIV/AIDS service organizations, 1991-1992; cuid8193 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Funding application pack, Red Hot AIDS Charitable Trust, 1994; cuid8194 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - General Journal Transaction Edit List, November 1999; cuid8195 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - General Journal Transaction Edit List, 2002; cuid8196 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - General ledger, 1996; cuid8197 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - General ledger, 1997; cuid8198 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - General ledger, 1998; cuid8199 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - General ledger, 1999; cuid8200 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - General ledger, 1999; cuid8201 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - General ledger, 1999, 2001; cuid8202 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002; cuid8203 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002; cuid8204 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002; cuid8205 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Giancarlo & Glieberman, 1990-1994; cuid8206 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Government Money Market Mutual Fund, 1996-2002; cuid8207 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Grants, 2001-2002; cuid8208 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Income, 1994-1997; cuid8209 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Information Document Request (IRS), 1997; cuid8210 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Information Document Request (IRS), 1997; cuid8211 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Information request, 1994; cuid8212 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, 1994-1999; cuid8213 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1994-1999; cuid8214 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, 2000-2001; cuid8215 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Intra-organization correspondence re: general accounts/cashflow, 1992; cuid8216 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Invitation list for Young Soul Rebels premiere, 1991; cuid8217 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Invoice approval requests/forms, 1991-1992; cuid8218 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Invoices, 2000; cuid8219 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Invoices: "Not Entered", 2000-2002; cuid8220 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Contains invoices relating to Red Hot + Indigo and Red Hot + Riot.
    - Invoices: amfAR, 1996; cuid8221 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Invoices: Barclays Bank, [n.d.]; cuid8222 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Invoices: Cinram International Inc., 2002; cuid8223 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Invoices: Inter-company (Restricted), 1994; cuid8224 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Invoices: Martin Greene Ravden, 1992 - 1995; cuid8225 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1992; cuid8226 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Invoices: Red Hot & Movin', 1992; cuid8227 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - IRS - Correspondence, 1994-1995; cuid8228 (Box 25, Folder 20)